Prepare to be terrified again.
Terrifier 3 is a horror, thriller film directed by Damien Leone.
Five years after surviving Art the Clown's Halloween massacre, Sienna and
Jonathan are still struggling to rebuild their shattered lives.
As the holiday season approaches, they try to embrace the Christmas
spirit and leave the horrors of the past behind.
But just when they think they're safe, Art returns, determined to
turn their holiday cheer into a new nightmare.
The festive season quickly unravels as Art unleashes his twisted
brand of terror, proving that no holiday is safe.
Sienna Shaw, played by Lauren LaVera.
Art the Clown, played by David Howard Thornton.
Victoria Heyes, played by Samantha Scaffidi.
Jonathan Shaw, played by Elliott Fullam.
Jessica, played by Margaret Anne Florence.
Greg, played by Bryce Johnson.
Terrifier 3 is a 2024 American independent Christmas slasher film
co-produced, written, edited, and directed by Damien Leone.
It is the sequel to Terrifier 2 (2022) and the third
installment in the Terrifier film series.
The film stars David Howard Thornton, Lauren LaVera,
Elliott Fullam, and Samantha Scaffidi.
On the days leading up to Christmas, Sienna Shaw attempts to rebuild her life, while pursued
by Art the Clown alongside his new accomplice, a possessed Victoria Heyes.
Following the critical and commercial success of Terrifier 2, Leone began
writing for the third film with plans for an overarching narrative.
Leone wanted to feature Victoria more prominently, as he regretted
leaving the character underdeveloped in the first film.
Principal photography began in February 2024 on a $2
million budget, and wrapped that April.
Terrifier 3 premiered at Fantastic Fest on September 19, 2024, and was theatrically released
in the United States on October 11, by Cineverse and Iconic Events Releasing.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and was a commercial success, grossing $90.3 million, becoming the
highest-grossing unrated film of all time, Cineverse's highest-grossing film, and the highest-grossing film of the franchise.
A fourth film, Terrifier 4, is in development.
The film explores themes of monster, post-traumatic stress
disorder (ptsd), angel, shower, child murder.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.